♪No matter how far the road is, don’t be afraid♪
♪ 길이 아무리 멀더라 도 두려워하지 마세요 ♪
♪Love is as gentle as longing ♪
♪사랑은 그리움 만큼 온화해요 ♪
♪The scars will definitely scab♪
♪상처는 반드시 딱지를 남깁니다♪
♪Funds become the flower of time♪
♪시간의 꽃이 될 펀딩♪
♪Eventually someone will quote it for you♪
♪결국 누군가가 당신을 위해 그것을 인용할 것입니다♪
♪Keep going, you won’t be alone♪
♪계속 전진하세요. 당신은 혼자가 아닙니다♪
♪Dialogue with the times♪
♪시대를 이야기하다♪
♪The light of response falls gently♪
♪빛이 이에 반응하여 부드럽게 떨어졌습니다♪
♪May you have him in your world♪
♪당신의 바다의 사람들이 그를 가질 수 있기를 ♪
♪Happiness like green tea and rooftops♪
♪녹차와 지붕 같은 행복♪
♪You know, life is full of regrets♪
♪인생은 후회로 가득 차 있잖아요 ♪
♪Masih menu♪
♪마시 메뉴카이♪
♪Winter and summer♪
♪겨울과 여름♪
[Panakea Cinta] [Vol. 10]
[파나케아 신타] [10화]
[2022 Sichuan Provincial Literature and Art Project Funded Works]
[ 2022년 쓰촨성 문학예술사업 지원 작품 ]
[Adapted from the lemon language novel "Panakea Cinta"]
[ 레몬 위얀의 소설 '파나케아 신타'를 각색함]
slower.
조금 천천히 하세요.
Slow down, Fang Mingfan.
천천히 하세요, 팡밍판.
This is a mountain road.
이것은 산길입니다.
scared?
두려워하는?
I'm not afraid.
나는 두렵지 않다.
You still want to go with me.
당신은 아직도 나와 함께 가고 싶어합니다.
If something happens to us,
우리에게 무슨 일이 생기면,
How can we save Vian and the Doctor? Gu?
웨이안 박사와 웨이안 박사를 어떻게 구하나요? 구?
If you follow our very slow pace...
우리의 아주 느린 속도를 따라가면 ...
slower.
조금 천천히 하세요.
We thought it would be nice if we could arrive before dawn.
새벽 전에 도착하면 좋겠다고 생각했어요 .
What should we do?
우리는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
Their cell phones must be out of battery.
그 사람들의 휴대폰은 배터리가 부족했나 봐요.
I called them earlier but that also failed.
아까 전화했는데 역시 실패했어요.
cannot.
할 수 없습니다.
The young boss never gave up on me.
그 젊은 상사는 결코 나를 포기하지 않았습니다.
I can't live without him either.
나도 그 사람을 떠날 수 없어요.
What does "give up on you" mean?
"너를 포기하다"은(는) 무슨 뜻인가요?
Why should I give up on you?
왜 당신을 포기합니까?
Didn't you ask?
물어보지 않았나요?
What is the mortality rate for the surgery I have ?
내가 수행한 수술의 사망률은 얼마나 됩니까 ?
I said before that I didn't record.
예전에는 녹음을 안 한다고 했어요.
In fact, during my first surgery...
사실 첫수술인데..
The patient died on the operating table.
환자는 수술대에서 사망했습니다.
That night...
그날 밤...
The patient's vital signs are unstable.
환자의 활력 징후가 불안정합니다.
Blood pressure 82/48 mmHg.
혈압은 82/48mmHg입니다.
Blood oxygen saturation is 70%.
혈중 산소 포화도 70%.
This is a blood blister aneurysm.
이것은 혈액 수포 동맥류입니다.
Bleeding spots must be treated immediately.
출혈 부위는 즉시 치료해야 합니다.
How long until the Doctor arrives?
박사님이 오기까지 얼마나 남았나요? 그 사람 왔나요?
PhD. He still has diarrhea.
박사. 그는 아직도 설사를 하고 있습니다.
Director Zhang is also performing another operation.
장 과장도 또 다른 작전을 펼치고 있다.
Blood oxygen saturation is below 70%.
혈중 산소 포화도 가 70% 미만입니다.
The amount of bleeding has exceeded 1000 ml.
출혈량이 1,000밀리리터를 넘었습니다.
Can't wait any longer.
더 이상 기다릴 수 없습니다.
Perform surgery immediately.
즉시 수술을 시행합니다.
PhD. He just asked you
박사. 그 사람이 방금 너한테 물었어
Maintain patient's vital signs.
환자의 활력징후를 유지한다.
If you operate now,
지금 운영한다면,
You must take responsibility for this operation.
이 수술은 네가 책임져야 해 .
Blood vesicle aneurysm.
혈액 물집 동맥류.
This is the most difficult and risky surgery .
이것은 가장 어렵고 위험한 수술이다 .
Can you do it?
당신은 그것을 할 수 있습니다?
if i don't try
내가 노력하지 않으면,
He will definitely die.
그는 반드시 죽을 것이다.
Perform surgery immediately.
즉시 수술을 시행합니다.
Absorbent gelatin sponge.
흡수성 젤라틴 스폰지.
The patient was in shock and required immediate blood transfusion.
환자는 쇼크 상태에 있어 즉시 수혈이 필요합니다.
The patient's heart stopped.
환자의 심장 박동이 멈췄습니다.
Perform cardiopulmonary resuscitation (CPR) immediately.
즉시 심폐소생술(CPR)을 실시합니다 .
PhD. It's funny if he doesn't come
박사. 그 사람은 안 오는 게 재미있어요.
The patient is dying,
환자가 죽어가고 있고,
what can I do?
어떡해?
Don't you want me to let him die?
내가 그 사람을 죽게 내버려두는 걸 원하지 않나요?
You only had surgery.
수술만 받으셨습니다.
Never had aneurysm surgery.
동맥류 수술을 한 적이 없습니다 .
How can you do this without permission?
허락도 없이 어떻게 그럴 수 있나요 ?
Fortunately, the patient's family members are reasonable and do not blame you.
다행히 환자 가족들은 합리적이고 당신을 비난하지 않습니다.
Take a good look at yourself.
당신은 자신을 잘 살펴보십시오.
No matter what you say, he can't even deal with an aneurysm.
당신이 무슨 말을 하든 그는 동맥류조차 치료할 수 없습니다.
How dare he perform surgery without waiting for the attending doctor.
감히 담당 의사를 기다리지도 않고 수술을 하게 된 거죠.
Why should he perform well?
그는 왜 멋진 연기를 하고 싶어 하는 걸까?
PhD. He said that some people
박사. 그가 말하길 어떤 사람들은
No talent. Just become a surgeon.
직접 외과의사가 될 만큼의 재능은 없습니다 .
I think in our unit,
내 생각엔 우리 부대에서는
No medical team dared to admit him.
어떤 의료팀도 감히 그를 받아들이지 못합니다.
(Try what you say, he can't even handle an aneurysm.)
(당신 말을 들어보세요. 그는 동맥류도 치료할 수 없습니다.)
(How dare he perform surgery without waiting for the attending doctor.)
(어떻게 감히 담당의사를 기다리지 않고 수술을 하게 됐는지.)
(Why does he have to act so well?)
(그는 왜 그렇게 멋진 연기를 하고 싶어 하는 걸까?)
(Dr. He said that some people)
(박사님이 그러셨는데 어떤 분들은)
(There is no natural talent for being a direct surgeon .)
( 직접 외과 의사가 될 재능이 없습니다.)
(I think in our unit,)
(저희 부대에서는 그런 것 같아요)
(No medical team dares to admit him now .)
(그 어떤 의료팀도 더 이상 감히 그를 받아들일 수 없습니다.)
(You only had surgery.)
(당신은 수술만 했습니다.)
( Aneurysm surgery has never been performed .)
( 동맥류 수술을 받은 적이 없습니다.)
(How can you do this without permission?)
허가 없이 어떻게 그럴 수 있나요?)
(Fortunately, the patient’s family members are reasonable and don’t blame you.)
(다행히 환자 가족분들이 합리적이고 원망하지 않으십니다.)
(Take a good look at yourself.)
(당신 자신을 잘 살펴보세요.)
(Try what you say, he can't even handle an aneurysm.)
(당신 말을 들어보세요. 그는 동맥류도 치료할 수 없습니다.)
(How dare he perform surgery without waiting for the attending doctor.)
(어떻게 감히 담당의사를 기다리지 않고 수술을 하게 됐는지.)
(Why does he have to act so well?)
(그는 왜 그렇게 멋진 연기를 하고 싶어 하는 걸까?)
(Why did he die?)
(그는 왜 죽었나요?)
At that time everyone thought my career was over,
그 당시에는 모두가 내 경력이 끝났다고 생각했지만
Including myself.
나 자신을 포함하여.
So, dr. Can I help you in the future?
그래서 박사님. 그 후에는 도와주실 거죠?
Do you know why I keep calling him little boss?
내가 왜 그 사람을 항상 젊은 상사라고 부르는지 아세요 ?
He's only two levels above me.
그 사람은 나보다 고작 두 단계 높았어요 .
But he and I are completely opposite people.
하지만 그와 나는 완전히 반대입니다.
His first surgery made him famous.
그의 첫 수술은 그를 유명하게 만들었습니다.
Presided over thalamic tumor surgery when he was young
그는 어린 나이에 시상 종양 수술을 주도했습니다.
Become a legend in the Neurosurgery Department of Huaren Hospital.
그리고 화렌병원 신경외과 에서 전설이 되었습니다 .
I just don't think so
난 그냥 그렇게 생각하지 않았어
He will tell useless people
그는 쓸모없는 사람들에게 말할 것입니다
So that everyone ignored it,
모두가 무시하는 것,
About to resign and change fields...
사임 하고 분야를 바꾸려고 합니다..
"You're unhappy."
"당신은 화가 났어요."
"I need an assistant."
"조수가 필요해요."
Fang Mingfan.
팡밍판.
why are you back
왜 돌아왔어?
What?
무엇?
I mean since you have decided to give up
내 말은, 당신이 포기하기로 결정했기 때문에,
Why are you still coming to the hospital?
왜 아직도 병원에 옵니까?
I am used to it.
나는 그것에 익숙하다.
Maybe this is also instinct.
어쩌면 본능이기도 합니다.
Fang Mingfan.
팡밍판.
Regarding transnasal sphenoidal approach to pituitary tumor surgery,
경비경접근법을 통한 뇌하수체 종양 수술에 대하여 ,
How much do you understand
당신은 얼마나 이해하고 있나요?
I used to study video
동영상을 공부하곤 했어요
And have seen some lecturers do this.
일부 강사가 그렇게 하는 것을 보았습니다 .
So, I'm sorry to upset you.
그럼, 기분 나쁘게 해서 미안해요.
I need a senior assistant.
수석 조수가 필요해요.
I can.
저 할 수 있어요.
Then the little boss also came to help with the charity work here.
그러다가 젊은 상사가 자선 활동을 돕기 위해 이곳에 왔습니다.
I don't want it either
나도 원하지 않는다
Face those who point fingers at China.
중국에서 손가락질하는 사람들과 마주합니다 .
So, I followed him here.
그래서 나는 그를 따라 여기까지 왔습니다.
So from that point on, Dr. Gu,
그래서 그 이후로 박사님. 구,
From a senior boss to a young boss?
선배에서 젊은 상사로 바뀌나요?
So, why is he so partial to you?
그렇다면 그 사람은 왜 당신에게 그렇게 편파적인가요?
I once asked him why he chose me.
한번은 그에게 왜 나를 선택했는지 물었습니다.
He is not partial.
그는 편파적이지 않습니다.
He said he didn't want to see defectors.
그는 탈북자들을 만나고 싶지 않다고 말했다 .
He doesn't like defectors.
그는 탈북자를 좋아하지 않습니다.
after that?
이후?
When will you start again?
언제 다시 시작할 거예요 ?
Second surgery?
두 번째 수술?
I'm not ready yet.
아직 준비가 안 됐어요.
I know I'm useless.
나는 내가 쓸모없다는 것을 안다.
Do not say.
그렇게 말하지 마.
You are useless, not as bad as me.
당신은 쓸모없고 나만큼 나쁘지도 않습니다.
If you are not ready yet,
준비가 안 되셨다면,
So it takes time to prepare.
그러니 준비하는 데 시간을 투자하세요.
Life is so long, there will definitely be a next time.
인생은 너무 길어서 반드시 다음이 있을 것이다.
There will definitely be a next time.
다음번에는 꼭 있을 겁니다.
I think the mobile charity clinic is just ahead,
이동식 자선 진료소 가 코앞인 것 같은데,
We are here waiting for them.
우리는 여기서 그들을 기다리고 있습니다.
Wait until it gets a little lighter before continuing the search.
검색을 계속하기 전에 약간 더 밝은 날을 기다리십시오 .
Mali.
마리.
Be careful.
조심하세요.
May I?
괜찮나요?
I have nothing.
나는 아무것도 없다.
Gu Yunzheng.
구윤정.
Bangun, Gu Yunzheng.
반군, 구윤정.
Don't fall asleep.
잠들지 마십시오.
Don't worry.
걱정 하지마.
I didn't pass out.
나는 기절하지 않았습니다.
I'm just sleepy.
그냥 졸려요.
Doing charity therapy all day
하루종일 자선치료를 해왔다
The road is so long.
그리고 길이 너무 길어요.
Really tired.
정말 피곤하다.
If you feel uncomfortable,
불편함을 느끼신다면,
must tell me yes
나한테 그렇다고 말해야 해
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
to be honest,
솔직히 말하자면,
I'm glad you took care of me.
당신이 나를 돌봐줘서 기뻐요.
so,
그래서,
If you feel uncomfortable,
불편함을 느끼신다면,
I'll just say it.
난 그냥 솔직하게 말할게.
Rest first.
먼저 쉬십시오.
This cannot go on.
이렇게 계속할 수는 없습니다.
I went to the rescuers.
구조대원을 찾으러 갔습니다.
wait for me here.
당신은 나를 여기서 기다리고 있습니다.
Be careful, Su Wei'an.
조심하세요, 수 웨이안.
quickly.
빠른.
hurry up.
어서 해봐요.
Situ.
현장.
Gu Yunzheng.
구윤정.
wake up.
깨우다.
I was shocked.
나는 충격을 받았습니다.
You are really strong.
당신은 정말 강해요.
How are you?
괜찮으세요?
I really don't want to wake up.
정말 일어나고 싶지 않아요.
If only you'd wake me up in two seconds
2초 뒤에 나를 깨웠더라면 ,
i can kiss you
난 네게 키스 할수있어
so far.
지금까지.
Next time if you have this kind of dream again, don't involve me anymore.
다음에는 이런 꿈을 꾼다면 저를 끌어들이지 마세요.
how?
어떻게?
You are busy with everything,
당신은 모든 일에 바쁘다.
Get ready to get busy again and figure out other people's dreams.
다른 사람들의 꿈을 다시 찾으려고 바쁠 준비가 되어 있습니다 .
Wei'an.
웨이안.
quickly.
빠른.
Please carry him inside.
그를 안으로 들어 올려주세요.
What happened to the young boss?
젊은 상사에게 무슨 문제가 있는 걸까요?
what happen?
무슨 일이야?
【Friendly Hospital】
[친절한 병원]
you're awake.
당신은 깨어있습니다.
How do you feel now?
당신은 지금 기분이 어떻게?
Thirsty.
갈증.
Drink water first.
먼저 물을 마셔보세요.
Drinking plenty of water can boost your metabolism.
물을 많이 마시면 ​​신진 대사가 증가할 수 있습니다.
hungry.
배고픈.
Do you want to eat porridge?
죽을 먹고 싶니?
Unable to wake up.
깨어날 수 없습니다.
It doesn't matter. I don't want to eat it.
괜찮아. 나는 그것을 먹고 싶지 않다.
I bribe you.
나는 당신에게 뇌물을 줍니다.
Mali.
마리.
You picked me up.
당신이 나를 데리러 왔어요.
am I wrong?
내가 잘못?
Wei'an sedang suap Dr. Gu.
웨이안 세당 수압 구 박사.
both of them
그 둘은
What to do in Kampung Rabe at night ?
Kampung Rabe에서는 밤에 무엇을 하시나요 ?
Vian looked like a different person.
웨이안은 다른 사람 처럼 보였습니다 .
PhD. me too.
박사. 나도 같아.
While in the village, they would not
마을에 있는 동안에는 그렇지 않습니다.
eat any kind of fruit
어떤 종류의 과일이라도 먹어라
Will it be poisoned like this?
이렇게 중독되려고?
Good morning, Sister Lan.
좋은 아침이에요, 란 씨.
Why are you making a video call to your mom?
엄마한테 영상통화는 왜 하는 거야 ?
I'm already late for dancing in the square.
나는 광장에 춤을 추러 가기에 늦었다 .
Square dance?
광장에서 춤을 추나요?
Isn’t it Beijing time now?
지금은 베이징 시간이 아닌가?
Is it only eight o'clock in the morning?
아직 아침 8시야?
Workers don’t even get up that early.
노동자들은 그렇게 일찍 일어나지도 않습니다.
Well, I chatted with you for a while.
글쎄요, 잠시 얘기를 나눴어요.
wrong.
사실이 아니다.
Today is the weekend,
오늘은 주말이에요,
You're just sitting in the hospital.
넌 그냥 병원에 앉아있어.
If there is no class, you take a test.
수업이 없으면 테스트만 하면 됩니다.
At least, go to the library and sit.
최소한 도서관에 가서 앉으세요.
You came to France in vain,
헛되이 당신은 프랑스에 있습니다.
I don’t want to just enjoy life.
나는 인생을 직접적으로 즐기고 싶지 않습니다.
Who said I am in the hospital every day?
내가 매일 병원에 간다고 누가 그랬나요?
Last week, I went to the village for a charity therapy session.
지난주에는 마을 지역에 자선 치료를 진행하러 다녀왔습니다 .
Feel the experience and atmosphere of the French countryside
프랑스 시골의 경험과 분위기를 느껴보세요
and the customs and habits of the local people.
현지 사람들의 관습도 그렇고.
You treat villagers instead of going to the hospital,
병원 대신 마을 사람들을 치료하고 ,
There is no difference.
아무런 차이가 없습니다.
You see, your skin has darkened.
보세요, 당신의 피부는 이미 어두워졌습니다.
Women must be good at taking care of their skin.
여자들은 피부관리를 잘해야 합니다.
Take a look, what is this?
이게 뭔지 알아?
Sun protection.
태양 보호.
Spray every two hours.
2시간에 한 번씩 뿌리세요.
I'm telling you, don't be so stingy.
내가 말하는데, 너무 인색하지 마세요.
Cheaper than future whitening injections.
나중에 미백주사를 맞아야 하는 것보다 저렴해요 .
Yes I know.
응, 알아요.
I don't go to charity therapy every day .
제가 자선 치료를 받으러 가는 것이 매일 있는 것은 아닙니다 .
I'm not exposed to the sun every day.
나는 매일 햇빛에 노출되지 않습니다 .
So, why does the skin turn dark?
그렇다면 피부는 왜 어두워지는 걸까요?
run out,
다 떨어지고,
It should be caused by age factor.
연령 요인 때문일 것입니다.
There is something wrong with your metabolism.
신진대사에 문제가 있습니다 .
metabolism?
대사?
I'm not even 30 yet.
저는 아직 30세가 되지 않았습니다.
Until my heart said this to my son.
내 마음이 내 아들에게 그렇게 말할 때까지.
You don’t compare with me.
당신은 나와 비교하지 않습니다.
My genes are so good
내 유전자가 너무 좋다.
Every time we go out,
우리는 밖에 나갈 때마다,
People always say we are like brothers and sisters.
사람들은 항상 우리가 형제 자매 같다고 말합니다.
Who has such poor eyesight?
누구의 시력이 그렇게 나쁜가요?
Come on, what's the matter?
서둘러요, 무슨 일이에요?
there is nothing.
아무것도 아님.
I miss my mother.
엄마가 그리워요.
When I go to charity therapy
자선치료를 받으러 갔을 때,
i saw a girl
나는 여자를 봤어
He only lives with his mother
그는 어머니와만 살고 있어요.
So I suddenly missed my mother.
그래서 갑자기 엄마가 그리워요.
Do you still have time to miss me?
아직도 나를 그리워할 시간이 있나요?
I mean, you have a lot of time.
내 말은, 당신은 시간이 많다는 거죠.
You don't have a boyfriend, right?
너 남자친구 없는 거 맞지?
Every time I talk to my mother
엄마랑 얘기할 때마다
We will end up discussing the same topic.
결국 같은 주제 에 대해 이야기하겠습니다 .
Why don't you ask me?
왜 나한테 물어보지 않았어?
Is it difficult or not difficult to travel abroad?
해외에 앉아있는 것이 어렵거나 그렇지 않습니까?
You are the one who is looking for this article.
기사를 찾고 계시는 분입니다.
I gave birth to you and you are so beautiful.
나는 당신을 너무 아름답게 낳았습니다.
i don't want you
나는 당신을 원하지 않는다
Face test equipment every day.
매일 테스트 장비를 마주합니다 .
You know what people call this?
사람들이 이것을 무엇이라고 부르는지 아시나요?
What a waste of beautiful youth.
청춘의 아름다운 청춘을 낭비하세요.
OK
좋아요.
Mom wins.
엄마가 이겼어요.
I am an open-minded mother.
나는 열린 마음을 가진 엄마 입니다.
I just want you to feel loved.
나는 단지 당신이 사랑을 느끼기를 바랍니다.
It doesn't matter what the result is.
결과가 어떻든 상관없습니다 .
What matters is the process.
중요한 것은 과정입니다.
Don’t you want to wait until you are 70 or 80 years old?
70, 80세가 될 때까지 기다리고 싶지 않으신가요 ?
Did you fall in love when you were old?
너는 늙어서 사랑에 빠졌니 ?
It felt like mom wanted sex.
사랑을 나누고 싶은 엄마 같은 느낌이에요.
what are you saying?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
Brother Lan.
란 형제.
You don’t feel that much of a burden.
별로 부담감을 느끼지 않으세요.
I have no opinion.
나는 의견이 없습니다.
I'm just an ordinary person, I don't want to talk anymore
나는 평범한 사람입니다. 더 이상 이야기하고 싶지 않습니다.
I really don't have time.
정말 시간이 없었어요.
Young boss.
젊은 상사.
We have two weeks left in our charity work
자선 활동이 2주 남았습니다.
will expire.
만료됩니다.
All these explanatory documents,
이 모든 설명 문서는,
Please fill in quickly
빨리 채워주세요
The hospital asked,
병원에서 물어보니,
we want to apply
우리는 신청하고 싶어요
Continue to perform medical assistance missions next year
내년에도 의료 지원 임무를 계속하기 위해
Or want to go back to China?
아니면 중국으로 돌아가고 싶나요?
Anything else?
다른 것이 있나요?
The infirmary also asked me to remind you,
진료실에서도 상기시켜달라고 부탁했는데,
Before the crew came to Lakaya on a rescue mission,
선원들이 라카야 구호 임무에 오기 전,
On the stalled glioma program.
중단된 신경교종 프로젝트에 대해.
After He Xiaoguang took over,
허샤오광이 취임한 후,
Still no progress.
아직 진전이 없습니다.
If this situation continues,
이것이 계속된다면,
You will not be able to apply for scientific research funding for the next year.
그러면 더 이상 다음 해 연구비를 신청할 수 없습니다 .
The other one is about the Young Talents Program.
또 하나는 청년 인재 프로젝트에 관한 것인데,
Held every four years.
4년마다 실시됩니다.
if you don't come back
만약 돌아오지 않는다면,
It is very likely that it will be taken away by He Xiaogong.
아마도 He Xiaogung이 가져갈 것입니다.
So now do we want to go back or not?
그럼 이제 돌아갈까요, 말까요?
Young boss.
젊은 상사.
if we go back to china
중국으로 다시 돌아가면,
What will happen between you and Wei An ?
당신과 웨이안 사이에 무슨 일이 일어날까요 ?
you two,
너희 둘 다,
Have you confirmed the relationship?
이미 관계를 확인하셨나요?
If you return to China,
중국에 다시 가게 된다면,
Will he come or not?
그 사람이 따라올까, 말까?
Jiang Muying asked you to ask?
Jiang Muying이 물어 보라고 했나요?
I...I'm just worried.
난... 그냥 걱정이 돼서요.
You're too busy pretending that your leg isn't healed yet
아직 다리 안 낫은 척 하느라 바쁜데
It's also difficult
너무 힘들어
correct?
오른쪽?
Isn't my leg healed yet?
내 다리는 아직도 낫지 않았나요?
Look at my beautiful legs.
내 아름다운 다리를 보세요.
I'm just kidding.
농담이야.
Your legs haven't healed yet, so don't move them too much.
다리는 아직 낫지 않았으니 너무 많이 움직이지 마세요.
It doesn't matter.
괜찮아.
Still sick?
아직도 아픈가요?
It hurts, really hurts.
아파요, 정말 아파요.
it does not matter.
이것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Recently,
요 며칠,
you can have surgery
수술하면 돼요
Why is it still so bad?
왜 아직도 그렇게 나쁜가요?
You can sit near the operating table,
수술대 근처에 앉을 수 있고,
So my legs won't be affected too much.
그래서 내 다리는 그다지 영향을 받지 않습니다 .
why are you laughing?
왜 웃어요?
Fang Mingfan.
팡밍판.
Don't you have an emergency?
긴급상황이 없으신가요?
When is my time...
내 시간은 언제인가...
that's right.
좋아요.
I have an emergency.
긴급 상황이 생겼습니다.
Look at the young boss.
젊은 사장님 좀 봐주세요.
[Gu Yunzheng]
[구윤정]
Surgery can still be performed,
아직 수술이 가능하고,
It seems that your problem is not serious.
문제가 그다지 심각하지 않은 것 같습니다.
Take a break.
휴식을 취하세요.
wait.
기다리다.
After taking my white coat, do you want to leave?
내 흰색 가운을 입고 그냥 갈래?
The lounge is too cold, I...
휴게실이 너무 추워서...
Just be careless.
그냥 함부로 가져가세요.
Did you just take it away accidentally?
그냥 함부로 받아요?
My legs hurt because of you.
너 때문에 다리가 아프다 .
Do you want to pretend you don't know?
모르는 척 하고 싶나요?
After that, what more do you want?
그 후에는 또 무엇을 원하시나요?
You must have studied in college,
대학시절 공부하셨을 텐데요 ,
In human saliva,
인간의 타액에서
There is something called opiorphin.
오피르핀이라는 것이 있습니다 .
this material
이 자료
Has analgesic effects comparable to morphine .
모르핀과 비슷한 진통 효과를 나타냅니다 .
this means,
그 의미는,
Direct kissing can help relieve pain.
직접 키스하면 통증 완화에 도움이 될 수 있습니다.
If you live long you can see anything.
오래 살았다면 무엇이든 볼 수 있다.
Unexpectedly, this noble and cold little boss
이렇게 고상하고 차가운 젊은 상사가 있을 줄은 몰랐어요
One day you will be rejected.
언젠가는 거절당할 것이다.
Are you really bored?
정말 지루해요?
Do you want to take care of the emergency department for a week straight?
일주일 연속 응급실을 돌보고 싶으신가요 ?
sorry for interrupting you.
방해해서 미안해.
♪Love requires honesty♪
♪사랑은 솔직해야 해요♪
Please do not make loud noises in the hospital.
병원에서는 소음을 내지 마십시오.
Quiet.
고요.
[Jinhai City]
[반다르진하이]
[Wen Ran]
[웬란]
Yuncheng.
윈청.
My father invites you to his house for dinner on the weekend
우리 아버지가 이번 주말에 당신 집에 식사하자고 초대하셨는데,
What do you want to eat?
너 뭐 먹고 싶니?
I can prepare the materials first
재료를 먼저 준비하면 돼요
Or we can go to the supermarket together.
아니면 같이 슈퍼마켓에 갈 수도 있어요.
I really enjoy going to the supermarket with you.
나는 당신과 함께 슈퍼마켓에 가는 것을 정말 좋아해요 .
[I want to go abroad, so I can’t come this weekend. 】
[해외로 나가야 해서 이번 주말에는 못 가요.]
Enter.
입력하다.
Director Du.
감독 두.
Have you booked the flight to Lakaya that I asked you to book?
제가 예약하라고 한 라카야행 티켓은 이미 예약 하셨나요 ?
Oh yeah.
오 예.
But I have something to report.
그런데 보고할 게 있어요 .
speak out.
발언.
Phase III clinical trial of HDQ39
HDQ39의 3상 임상시험
Started
시작했다
In order to increase the stock price,
주가 상승을 고려하여 ,
The Steering Committee would like to take this opportunity to hold a media conference.
운영위원회는 미디어 컨퍼런스를 개최할 기회를 갖고 싶습니다 .
Please sir, can you attend.
선생님 꼭 참석해주세요.
I held a press conference when I came back.
제가 돌아온 후 기자회견을 열어주세요 .
Recruitment will begin next week.
다음주부터 모집이 시작됩니다.
If you wait until later...
나중에 돌아올 때까지 기다리면...
for me.
나를 위한.
How committed are you to this project?
이 프로젝트에 얼마나 헌신하시나요 ?
The decision of the Board of Directors will be determined .
이사회의 결정을 내리게 됩니다 .
If you can attend the press conference in person,
기자간담회에 직접 참석하실 수 있다면 ,
The next phase of the financing process will be smoother.
다음 단계의 자금조달 과정은 더욱 원활해질 것입니다.
That's it, please cancel my ticket.
됐어요. 항공권을 취소해 주세요.
OK
좋아요.
【Friendly Hospital】 【Lakaya】
[친절한 병원] [라카야]
[Fang Mingfan] (Tapi sekarang, disebabkan Su Wei'an,)
[Fang Mingfan] (Tapi sekarang, disebabkan Su Wei'an,)
(He changed his mind again.)
(그는 다시 마음을 바꾼다.)
(Hesitates a little,)
(약간의 망설임,)
(I'll ask for more information later.)
(자세한 내용은 나중에 질문하겠습니다.)
[Gu Yunzheng]
[구윤정]
What to look at?
뭘 봐?
River,
장,
Among the beauty products you own ,
가지고 있는 뷰티 제품 중 ,
Are there any products that can brighten skin tone?
피부를 밝게 해주는 제품이 있나요 ?
Why do you suddenly want to brighten your skin tone?
갑자기 피부가 밝아지고 싶은 이유는 무엇인가요 ?
Didn't you always dislike me before?
예전에는 항상 나를 좋아하지 않았던 건 당신이 아니었나요 ?
Because I've been taking care of my skin?
내가 항상 피부를 관리하기 때문에?
Women beautify themselves for the person they like.
여자들은 자신이 좋아하는 사람들을 위해 자신을 아름답게 꾸미는 경향이 있습니다 .
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Awak dan Gu Yunzheng
Awak dan Gu Yunzheng
do what
무엇을 합니까
Two days and one night in the jungle ?
정글에서 1박 2일을 보내면서 ?
Didn't do anything.
아무것도 하지 않았습니다.
Right time, right place, right person. Everything is done.
적절한 시간, 적절한 장소, 적절한 사람들. 모든 것이 완료되었습니다.
I didn't expect you to seduce Gu Yunzheng.
나는 당신이 Gu Yunzheng을 유혹 할 수 있을 것이라고 생각하지 않았습니다 .
Romantic drama turns into a night of wilderness survival .
로맨틱 드라마는 야생 생존의 밤으로 변합니다 .
It's just a waste of fate,
운명을 낭비할 뿐이야
Be prepared for thunderstorms.
뇌우에 대비하세요.
No. What do you think about every day?
아니, 매일 무슨 생각을 하시나요 ?
Why do things happen between us?
왜 우리 사이에 무슨 일이 일어난 걸까요?
Sister, I'm worried about you.
언니, 걱정돼요.
If they don't seize this opportunity, they will want to return to China.
이 기회를 다시 잡지 않으면 중국으로 돌아가고 싶어 할 것입니다.
Go back to China?
중국으로 돌아가나요?
Why?
왜?
Fang Mingfan kata,
팡밍판카타,
Their medical assistance mission is coming to an end.
의료 지원 임무가 곧 종료됩니다.
So they will come back after that .
그래서 그들은 그 후에 다시 돌아올 것입니다 .
Didn't Gu Yunzheng tell you?
구윤정이 말하지 않았나요?
it should be.
그것은해야한다.
After all, you two
결국 너희 둘은
not together
함께 있지 않다
Although Kampong Rabe has such a good opportunity.
캄풍라베에 이렇게 좋은 기회가 있는데도 말이죠.
I think,
나는 느낀다,
He thinks you have no heart for him.
그는 당신이 그에게 마음이 없다고 생각합니다.
So he doesn't dare to take you back to China.
그래서 그는 감히 당신을 중국으로 데려갈 생각을 하지 못했습니다 .
I really don't understand you.
나는 정말로 당신을 이해하지 못합니다.
you say. He is tall and handsome.
당신은 그것을 말한다. 그 사람은 또 키가 크고 잘생겼어요.
He is also the person you liked before .
그 사람은 당신이 예전에 좋아했던 사람이기도 해요.
He is right in front of you,
그 사람이 바로 당신의 눈앞에 있고,
You just let him go?
그냥 놔뒀어?
I really hope,
정말 좋겠다.
For example, tomorrow is Judgment Day,
예를 들어 내일은 심판의 날이다.
This world is destroyed,
이 세상은 멸망했고,
I still want to have a great relationship.
나는 여전히 좋은 사랑의 관계를 갖고 싶습니다 .
If not, it's really a loss.
그렇지 않다면 정말 손해입니다.
I want to go back to China and he is still so close to me.
나는 중국으로 돌아가고 싶다. 그는 아직도 나와 너무 가깝다고 말한다.
What does it mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
How are you, have you ever thought about cooking?
잘 지내세요, 요리에 대해 생각해 보셨나요?
Where do we want to go?
우리는 어디로 가고 싶나요?
Keep moving.
계속 움직여.
You don't want to kidnap me, do you?
당신은 나를 납치하고 싶지 않습니까?
Have you seen the kidnapper sitting in the passenger seat?
조수석에 앉아있는 유괴범을 본 적이 있나요?
And let the hostages take the car?
인질이 차를 가져가게 놔두나요?
your leg is hurt
다리가 다쳤어요,
You were supposed to go to the hospital to rest, but you insisted on going out.
그냥 병원에서 쉬었어야 했는데, 나가겠다고 고집하셨어요.
Prepare to ask me to drive for you again .
다시 운전해 달라고 요청할 준비가 되었습니다 .
Didn't you let me use your car?
나에게 차를 이용하라고 한 사람이 당신이 아니었나요 ?
Do you want to get money?
돈을 받고 싶나요?
son.
아들.
So where exactly are we going?
그럼 우리는 정말 어디로 가는 걸까요?
I heard a story about a local tribe
어느 동네 씨족에 대한 이야기를 들었는데 ,
There is a reliable shaman,
믿음직한 무당이 있으니
Experts in the treatment of difficult and complicated diseases.
난치병 치료의 전문가 .
I want to go out there and get my legs checked out.
거기 가서 다리를 확인하고 싶어요 .
What?
무엇?
You are an associate professor at Huaren University.
당신은 Huaren의 부교수입니다.
Can you respect science?
과학을 조금 존중할 수 있습니까?
According to today’s modern medicine,
오늘날 현대 의학에 따르면,
My leg pain should be gone.
다리 통증이 나았어야 했어요.
But the problem now is that he hasn't recovered yet.
하지만 문제는 지금 까지도 그가 회복되지 않았다는 점이다.
I felt an evil energy entering my body.
몸에 사악한 기운이 들어가는 것 같아요 .
So if you follow,
그러니 따라해 보면,
This is something that modern medicine cannot explain.
현대의학으로는 설명할 수 없는 일이다 .
Therefore, we need to find another way.
그러므로 다른 방법을 생각해 볼 필요가 있습니다.
Go all the way to the end and turn right.
끝까지 직진한 후 우회전하세요.
As I said before, the fare is doubled.
아까 말했잖아, 자동차 요금을 두 배로 내라고.
Great, no problem.
좋아요, 문제 없어요.
Is this the shaman's house you're talking about?
여기가 당신이 말하는 무당의 집인가요 ?
Yes, it's a bit unique.
좀 독특해요, 그렇죠.
Did he go outside for treatment?
그 사람은 밖에서 환자를 치료하러 갔죠?
look,
알다시피,
Navigation brought me here.
내비게이션이 나를 여기로 데려왔다.
OK
좋아요.
I also want to find a shaman
나도 무당을 찾고 싶다.
Open a branch here.
여기에 지점을 개설하세요.
Mesra Hospital Untreatable Diseases,
메스라병원이 치료할 수 없는 것,
Asking for help Dr. Gu brought them here yes.
박사님에게 도움을 요청하세요 구가 여기로 데려오라고 그래.
You will definitely be able to make a lot of profits.
많은 수익을 낼 수 있어야 합니다.
I have no idea,
모르겠습니다,
This tree has a soul.
이 나무에는 영혼이 있어요.
you do not say,
당신은 말하지 않습니다,
my leg
내 이 다리,
I no longer feel pain. Look at this.
더 이상 고통을 느끼지 않습니다. 이걸 보세요.
hurry up.
어서 해봐요.
I'll take you to a place.
난 당신을 어딘가로 데려갈 거예요.
Look at that.
저것 봐.
really beautiful!
정말 아름답습니다!
This bridge was built by the Chinese.
이 다리는 중국인이 건설했습니다.
I have been in Lakaya for more than a year
라카야에 온지 1년이 넘었 는데 ,
I have passed through so many bridges built by the Chinese.
중국인이 건설한 수많은 다리를 건너왔습니다 .
Every time I think like this,
그런 생각이 들 때마다,
In all this there is not one or the other
이 모든 것에는 아무도 없습니다
Built by my mom.
엄마가 지은 거예요.
Of course there is.
물론 있습니다.
Your mother is a respectable woman.
어머니는 존경받아야 할 분이십니다.
that's right.
좋아요.
if she wasn't my mother
그 사람이 우리 엄마가 아니었다면,
perhaps
아마도
i will love him
나는 그를 사랑할 것이다
Let's ask him how he is.
그가 어떤지 물어보자.
Hello!
헬리콥터!
Are you OK?
어떻게 지내세요?
Is this a replica bridge?
이것은 레플리카 브릿지인가요?
It is said that a light festival is held here every year.
이곳에서는 매년 빛축제가 열린 다고 합니다 .
It’s just that I’ve lived in Lakaya for so long,
단지 제가 라카야에 너무 오랫동안 살아왔기 때문일 뿐입니다.
There is no chance to join yet.
아직 참여할 기회가 없습니다.
that's right.
좋아요.
Maybe it's because you are too busy looking for money.
어쩌면 돈을 찾느라 너무 바쁘기 때문일 수도 있습니다 .
You ran so fast just now,
방금 당신은 너무 빨리 달렸어요
Are your legs no longer sore?
다리는 이제 안 아프나요?
sick. Still uncomfortable.
아픈. 아직도 아프다.
Do you want to try it?
너 해보고 싶니?
Nothing wrong?
아무것도 없나요?
I tell you,
내가 말하건데,
This game releases the hormone dopamine in us,
이 경주는 우리가 도파민 호르몬을 분비하게 할 수 있습니다.
let's get excited
우리를 흥분하게 만들어
The same goes for having sex.
사랑을 나누는 것도 마찬가지다.
It seems that I am more effective than the shaman.
무당보다 제가 더 효과적인 것 같습니다 .
Your leg seems to be healed.
다리가 나은 것 같습니다.
Pay.
지불하다.
Why?
왜?
The hostage demands money from the kidnapper.
인질들은 납치범들에게 돈을 요구합니다.
You look more like a hostage than me .
당신은 나보다 인질처럼 보입니다 .
If you want money, there isn't any.
돈을 달라고 하면 아무것도 없습니다.
If you want this person, you can change it to yours.
그 사람을 원한다면 당신으로 바꿀 수 있습니다.
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
I didn't hear it.
나는 듣지 못했다.
You stopped performing again.
당신은 다시 행동을 중단했습니다 .
Didn't you hear?
들리지 않나요?
You guessed it.
당신은 그것을 짐작했다.
We are dizzy again.
우리는 또 어지러워진다.
hurry up!
서둘러요!
Suddenly out of nowhere,
갑자기, 난데없이,
When will this all be available?
이 모든 것이 언제 가능합니까?
That day was mountain time,
그날은 산에 갈 시간입니다.
I'm hungry, thirsty, and scared.
배고프고, 목마르고, 무서워요.
So I prepared a little earlier this time.
그래서 이번에는 조금 일찍 준비하세요.
Be prepared for any eventuality?
만일의 사태에 대비하고 계시나요?
this thing
이 물건
Essential for outdoor survival.
밖에서 생존하는 데 필수적입니다 .
Is this also important for surviving outside?
이것은 밖에서도 생존을 위해 중요하다?
You shouldn't underestimate this picnic mat.
이 피크닉 매트를 무시해서는 안됩니다 .
It is moisture-proof, waterproof and wear-resistant.
방습, 방수 및 내마모성입니다.
This is a must-have item
이건 꼭 가지고 있어야 할 아이템이에요
Go travel.
여행하다.
brother,
형제,
We are in the desert now .
우리는 지금 사막에 있습니다.
You talked to me about waterproofing and moisture-proofing.
방수 방습에 관해 말씀해 주셨는데요 .
Be prepared for any eventuality?
만일의 사태에 대비하고 계시나요?
This one too?
이것도?
Do you remember our time in the mountains?
우리가 산에서 보낸 시간을 기억하시나요 ?
Our cell phones are running out of battery, right?
우리 휴대폰은 모두 배터리가 부족해요. 그렇죠?
This type of battery will last longer. look.
이 유형의 배터리는 조금 더 오래 지속됩니다. 당신은 보인다.
oh.
오.
So what you mean is,
그러니까,
We'll hang it on ourselves later
나중에 몸에 걸게요
For lighting?
조명용?
You can hang it high.
높은 곳에 걸어두시면 됩니다 .
Try looking at it this way.
당신은 이것을 이렇게 보려고 노력합니다.
It would look beautiful if hung on a tent.
텐트에 걸어놓으면 정말 예쁠 것 같아요.
tent?
텐트?
Are you ready to bring your tent?
텐트를 가져올 준비가 되셨나요?
Wei An, are you thirsty?
웨이안아, 목마르니?
I saw you finished your drink.
술을 다 마 셨나 보군요 .
no.
아니다.
where is my water
내 물은 어디 있지?
Who turned it into alcohol?
누가 그걸 술로 만들었나?
no.
아니다.
(Alcohol gives people courage.)
(술은 용기를 준다.)
(You two are cowards.)
(너희 둘은 겁쟁이다.)
(I can only help so far.)
(지금까지만 도와드릴 수 있습니다.)
【Friendly Hospital】
[친절한 병원]
Obviously,
보기에,
Only drink.
술만 마실 수 있어요.
Quench your thirst.
갈증을 해소하세요.
Have some wine to quench your thirst.
갈증을 해소하기 위해 와인을 마셔보세요.
Very comfortable.
편안해요.
It feels like a long time ago
오래전 일처럼 느껴지네요
Not enjoying the tranquility of the night
밤의 고요함을 즐기지 못함
comfortably.
편안하게.
No need to think about anything.
아무것도 생각할 필요가 없습니다.
Just need to be quiet
그냥 조용히 있으면 돼
Enjoy the beauty of the night sky.
밤하늘의 아름다움에 감탄해보세요.
me too.
나도 같아.
I used to do this every day
예전에는 매일 그랬는데
Busy as a machine.
기계처럼 바쁘게 일한다.
But never stop and think for a moment
하지만 한 순간도 생각을 멈추지 마세요.
What do I work for?
나는 무엇을 위해 일합니까?
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
I've finished the wine and can't go back.
우리는 이미 포도주를 마셨으므로 더 이상 돌아갈 수 없습니다.
Don't worry.
걱정 하지마.
As long as I'm here, you're safe.
내가 여기 있는 한 당신은 안전할 거예요.
However, I also think that
하지만 내 생각에도,
You are the source of danger.
당신은 위험의 원인입니다.
Do you think I 've reached that point?
내가 그 정도까지 이르렀을 것 같아 ?
Although I love you,
나는 당신을 사랑하지만,
I won't take advantage of you either.
나도 당신을 이용하지 않을 것입니다.
But I will.
그러나 전 할겁니다.
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
No.
아니요.
OK
좋아요.
you are great too.
당신도 훌륭해요.
must be.
그래야합니다.
Taste it first.
먼저 맛보세요.
odor.
냄새.
use this.
이것을 사용하십시오.
No, I'm not cold either.
필요없어, 난 춥지도 않아.
Drinking alcohol can warm the body.
술을 마시면 몸이 따뜻해집니다.
OK
좋아요.
Hurry up and give it a try.
서둘러, 시도해 보세요.
let's go
갑시다
Cheers to beauty tonight.
오늘 밤 미용을 위해 마셔보세요.
OK
좋은.
drink!
마시다!
Why do we fight?
우리는 왜 싸우는가?
The winner may make one request.
승자는 한 가지 요청을 할 수 있습니다.
Against what?
무엇에 반대합니까?
Opponents look for zodiac signs.
반대자들은 별 조디악 표지판을 찾습니다.
Whoever can find the most people wins.
가장 많이 찾는 사람이 승리합니다.
how?
어떻게?
I was in an astronomy club in college.
나는 대학 시절 천문학 동아리에 가입하곤 했다 .
Do you really want to fight me?
정말 나랑 싸우고 싶은 거야 ?
Is it really great?
정말 대단해요?
I once took a tour group to the desert.
나는 한때 사막에서 여행 그룹을 이끌었습니다.
Clients taught me and I also learned Chinese and French.
고객분들이 가르쳐주셨고, 중국어와 프랑스어도 배웁니다.
Are these hearsays of yours credible?
당신이 알고 있는 이 소문을 믿을 만합니까?
Believe it or not, your opponent knows first.
믿거나 말거나는 상대가 먼저 알게 될 것이다.
Why?
왜?
Or do you think that lecturers lose to students?
아니면 강사가 학생들에게 진다고 생각하시나요 ?
Is your face watering?
얼굴에 물이 드시나요?
Classmate Su.
학생 수.
What kind of strange desire to win is this?
그냥 이기려는 이상한 욕망이 당신의 것 입니까?
Let's get in the car and go fight.
차에 앉아서 싸우자.
Bintang Orion.
빈탕 오리온.
how is it like?
어떤 종류의?
do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
Betelgeuse is a star
베텔게우스는 별이다
Bright orange, a thousand times larger than the sun.
태양보다 1000배나 큰 밝은 오렌지색 .
Betelgeuse...
베텔게우스...
The stars of Ursa Major and Ursa Minor.
큰곰자리 별, 큰곰자리 별.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Do you really want to fight?
정말 싸우고 싶나요?
Aren't you afraid of losing and crying behind you?
나중에 흐느껴 울 정도로 지는 게 두렵지 않나요 ?
If you haven't started looking yet,
아직 찾기 시작하지 않으셨다면,
You will definitely lose.
당신은 패배해야합니다.
OK
좋아요.
Now that I can find those two stars,
별 두 개를 찾을 수 있게 되었기 때문에 ,
Not hard to find...
찾기는 어렵지 않은데...
Draco star.
드레이코 스타.
Cassiopeia star.
별 카시오페이아.
Gemini, Auriga.
쌍둥이자리 별, 마차부 별.
Auriga?
아우리가 스타?
of.
의.
Did you come up with this name?
이 이름을 생각해냈나요?
Why should I create?
그나저나 나는 왜 창조한 걸까?
Skilled driver.
숙련된 전차병.
Where? Let me get closer.
어디? 근처에 보여주세요.
Situ.
현장.
Have you seen the brightest star?
가장 밝은 별이 보이나요 ?
Its name is Capella,
카펠라라고 하는데
It is one of the main stars in the constellation Auriga.
그것은 별자리 Auriga의 주요 별 중 하나입니다 .
A lonely star.
혼자 외로운 별.
what you see is
당신이 보는 것은
A pair of major stars.
한 쌍의 주요 스타.
They are a pair of twin stars.
그들은 한 쌍의 쌍성별입니다.
They are very close together in orbit .
궤도에서의 거리는 매우 가깝습니다.
They revolve around the same center of mass.
같은 질량 중심을 중심으로 서로 공전합니다 .
it mean,
그 뜻은,
They are not alone.
그들은 혼자가 아닙니다.
I said four stars before.
아까 제가 별 4개라고 했는데요.
You just said three, so I win.
방금 3개라고 했으니 내가 이겼어요.
Where could that be?
그게 어디 있을 수 있나요?
I haven't finished speaking yet.
아직 얘기가 안 끝났어요.
Did you say that?
그렇게 말했나요?
winner...
우승자...
♪Death Dialogue♪
♪죽은 대화♪
♪Innocent words♪
♪순진한 말♪
♪My eyes are falling♪
♪눈이 떨어졌어요♪
♪The warmth that enters the palm of your hand...♪
♪손바닥의 온기 속으로...♪
Already admitted it.
이미 인정하세요.
♪Heartbeat speeds up♪
♪심장이 빨리 뛴다♪
♪Shrouded in nightmares...♪
♪악몽에 휩싸여...♪
lose to you,
당신에게 지고,
I do.
나는 기꺼이.
♪Pelukan selamatkanku♪
♪Pelukan selamatkanku♪
♪Rashisham♪
♪라시아무♪
♪I listen to every word of your dream♪
♪당신이 꿈꾸는 모든 말을 들어드립니다♪
♪Secretly record laughter♪
♪웃음을 몰래 녹음해 보세요♪
♪Segala impianmu♪
♪세갈라 임피안무♪
♪Rashaku♪
♪라시아쿠♪
♪I forgot that I was once a desert island♪
♪ 내가 한때 무인도였다는 사실을 잊어버렸어요♪
♪I miss you for waiting so long♪
♪ 오래 기다리니 그리워요 ♪
♪ Tariq Bajuku ♪
♪타릭 바주쿠♪
♪Aku Sintamu♪
♪아쿠친타무♪
are you awake
깨어있니?
Stop pretending, I've seen it.
더 이상 그런 척하지 마세요. 이미 봤거든요.
Its daybreak.
새벽이다.
Did you sleep well last night?
어젯밤에 잘 잤어요?
Not too good, I feel like I’m going to sleep again.
별로 좋지 않아, 다시 자고 싶은 기분이 든다.
Which part is bad?
어떤 부분이 좋지 않은가요?
I can try again.
다시 시도해 볼 수 있어요.
Good, it's time to wake up.
아주 좋아요, 벌써 일어날 수 있어요.
Wei'an,
웨이안,
I want to hug you like this every day.
매일 이렇게 안아주고 싶어요 .
Medical rescue mission ends
의료지원 임무는 끝났고,
Hospital
병원
Will tell me to come back as soon as possible.
곧 다시 오라고 말할 거예요.
♪At night, turn the hands of the clock♪
♪밤에는 시계바늘을 움직여보세요♪
♪Noise is replacing silence♪
♪소음이 침묵을 대신하고 있습니다♪
♪We act out the meeting script♪
♪회의 대본을 연기합니다♪
♪The rainbow that decorates the night♪
♪밤을 장식하는 무지개♪
♪And the wind that passes through the desert♪
♪그리고 사막을 가르는 바람♪
♪Have been our witnesses♪
♪우리의 증인이 되었으면♪
♪We are all people lost in obscurity♪
♪우리는 모두 어둠 속에서 길을 잃은 사람들입니다♪
♪Find one out of a billion possibilities♪
♪ 수억 개의 가능성 중 하나를 찾아보세요♪
♪Trapped in a city called destiny ♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀 ♪
♪But still chasing stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don’t worry my beloved wanderer♪
♪걱정하지 마세요 내 사랑하는 길냥이♪
♪Hold a glass of wine to warm your lonely soul♪
♪ 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 해줄 와인 한 잔 ♪
♪Let me hug your crack♪
♪당신의 균열을 안아줄게요♪
♪You are as bright as a star♪
♪당신은 별처럼 빛나네요♪
♪Twinkle in the silence♪
♪말없이 깜빡깜빡♪
♪At night, turn the hands of the clock♪
♪밤에는 시계바늘을 움직여보세요♪
♪Noise is replacing silence♪
♪소음이 침묵을 대신하고 있습니다♪
♪We act out the meeting script♪
♪회의 대본을 연기합니다♪
♪The rainbow that decorates the night♪
♪밤을 장식하는 무지개♪
♪And the wind that passes through the desert♪
♪그리고 사막을 가르는 바람♪
♪Have been our witnesses♪
♪우리의 증인이 되었으면♪
♪We are all people lost in obscurity♪
♪우리는 모두 어둠 속에서 길을 잃은 사람들입니다♪
♪Find one out of a billion possibilities♪
♪ 수억 개의 가능성 중 하나를 찾아보세요♪
♪Trapped in a city called destiny ♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀 ♪
♪But still chasing stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don’t worry my beloved wanderer♪
♪걱정하지 마세요 내 사랑하는 길냥이♪
♪Hold a glass of wine to warm your lonely soul♪
♪ 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 해줄 와인 한 잔 ♪
♪Let me hug your crack♪
♪당신의 균열을 안아줄게요♪
♪You are as bright as a star♪
♪당신은 별처럼 빛나네요♪
♪Twinkle in the silence♪
♪말없이 깜빡깜빡♪